Riverdance: The Animated Adventure is a animation,
fantasy, music film directed by Eamonn Butler.
A young Irish boy named Keegan and Spanish girl named Moya journey into a magical world of the
Megaloceros Giganteus who teach them to appreciate Riverdance as a celebration of life.
Based on the stage show phenomenon of the same name and featuring Bill
Whelan’s multi-platinum Grammy Award-winning music.
Grandad / Patrick (voice), played by Pierce Brosnan.
Keegan (voice), played by Sam Hardy.
Moya (voice), played by Hannah Herman Cortes.
Penny (voice), played by Lilly Singh.
Benny (voice), played by Jermaine Fowler.
Gatekeeper (voice), played by John Kavanagh.
Riverdance: The Animated Adventure is a 2021 animated dance
adventure film inspired by the dance show Riverdance.
The film was made by Cinesite for River Productions and Aniventure.
Riverdance: The Animated Adventure was released in the United Kingdom on 28 May 2021, by Sky Cinema,
and was made available to stream on Netflix on 14 January 2022 in the United States.
The film explores themes of dance, grandparent grandchild
relationship, river, village, stage show.
The tone is lighthearted.